[Music]
let's do open in 60 seconds or less
today we are doing a Benzene reaction
and we're making this product over here
give it a try let me know what you think
all right so what I see I see a Hera
relationship so they're para to one
another what I need to do then if I want
parent only is I needed but this Groupon
first and then second I need to place my
NO2
after I place my carbon chain here which
is my turbutyl and then what I can do
this is a para directing only functional
group
so it's going to place the next group in
the Paris spot only that's going to be
my hno3 and h2so4
there you have it thanks for tuning in
and we'll see you next time